ARPIT KUMAR MISHRA

A technology enthusiast is interested in solving real-world problems. Also being Open Source Software Club former secretary with experience of organizing national level Hackathon. Open-source enthusiast. Skilled in Coding, Front-end Development, and Back-End Web Development. I have a Hackathon winning spree of 8 in a row. I'm energetic and able to handle multiple tasks on a daily basis

aarpit24@gmail.com

PUNE, INDIA

in linkedin.com/in/arpit-kumar-mishra

9919098303

arpitkumarmishra.in

github.com/arkumish

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Engineering (BE), Computer Science & Engineering

Army Institute of Technology, Pune 🗷

07/2017 - 05/2021 9.15 SGPA

Higher Secondary School

Army Public School, Faizabad

05/2015 - 05/2016 92.00 %

WORK EXPERIENCE

SDE Intern

UBS 🗷

06/2020 - 07/2020

Tasks

- Worked with automation & operation team for their smart log analytics tool and process automation.
- Tech stack: Shell Scripting, Java Script, Loom Systems

SDE Intern

Innovaccer 🗷

03/2020 - 05/2020

Tasks

- Worked on their Care As One project, A social networking platform for healthcare domain. Part of the core team which created this project from idea to working deployed website.
- Tech Stack: ReactJS with redux state management tool, SCSS for styling, Java Script

Backend developer

Lead School 🗷

12/2019 - 01/2020 Mumbai

Tasks

- Worked on a Company's Real-time Bus Tracking service for parents of school students.
- Tech Stack: Node.js/Express.js for server-side scripting. Socket.io for creating bus-room for real-time driver-parent interaction.
 MySQL database and Redis. Mocha.js for unit testing

LEADERSHIP AND EXPERIENCE

Secretary

Open Source Software Club (2019-20)

Organizing Head

National Level Hackathon, INNERVE-19

Member

College Street Play Team

SKILLS



PROJECTS

InternConnect

 A web-based solution to connect newly joined interns inside the organization. Helps them to solve their problems through the post, connect with other users, send messages to others. Act as a social networking platform for the organization. Tech Stack: MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJs, Materialize bootstrap

Anubhav: Experience sharing platform

 Created an interview experience-sharing platform for our college. Where anyone can write, read, and request interview experience of college seniors. Tech stack: ReactJs, NodeJs, mongoDB

SAHAYAK APP

 An android app developed using Cordova for the visually impaired and elderly person to find a bus on bus stop. The app runs offline using Bluetooth to know about bus route.

Library Auto Reissuer

 A headless web scrapping project to automate the library reissue procedure of our college. The project was build using a express js and puppeteer node module.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Winner Hackpion Hackathon by EY Global (01/2021)

Winner Vodafone-Idea Limited Codefest 2020 (02/2020)

First Runner Up Rural Education IIT Delhi Hackathon (01/2020)

Winner at NEC Transportation Hackathon (06/2019)

Winner EUREKA Hackathon (02/2019)

First Runner Up AGS Transact Hackathon (07/2019)

Winner Pasckathon PUNE Hackathon (03/2019)

First Runner Up NEC Gurugram Hackathon (08/2019)

National Finalist for Smart India Hackathon (03/2019)

INTERESTS

Sketching Painting Doodling